wego.co.in 2016-03-13

# Privacy Policy

## **What the Wego Privacy Policy Covers**

The Privacy Policy covers our treatment of personally identifiable information that we collect when you are on a site, web portal or web pages operated or owned by Wego or affiliated with Wego (“ **Wego Site** “), and when you use our services.

When using a Wego site, you may also use the services offered by other parties. In particular, payment systems are provided by third parties and the information you provide to facilitate payment are collected by such third parties and not Wego. This Wego Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or control, or to people that we do not employ or manage. Please check the privacy practices of these other companies or persons (if any) to understand how they treat the personally identifiable information that you provide to them and contact them if you have any concerns.

## **Information Collection and Use by Wego**

We collect personally identifiable information when you create an account with us or register to receive email newsletters or other offers and promotions. Once you register with us, theoretically you are no longer anonymous to us. In addition, we automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, Wego cookie information and the page you requested. 

We use information for three general purposes: to customise the advertising and content you see, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, and to contact you about specials and new products by sending you e mail alerts for new products, features, enhancements, special offers, contests, events of interest, and one-off marketing promotions. Such alerts may include marketing information about Wego, our subsidiaries or selected business partners.

## **Opt Out from Marketing Information**

Any email we send to you will contain an easy automated unsubscribe link so that you can opt-out of the subscription. Simply follow the indications in the email.

## **Information Sharing and Disclosure by Wego**

We will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone. We will send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people only when:

  * We have your consent to share the information;
  * We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested;
  * We need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of us to provide a product or service to you. (Unless we tell you differently, these companies do not have any right to use the personally identifiable information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us.);
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; or
  * We find that your actions on our web sites violate the Wego Terms of Service, or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services.

## **Cookies and Opting Out from the Use of Cookies**

Cookies are text files containing small amounts of information which are downloaded to your device when you visit a website. Cookies are sent back to the originating website on each subsequent visit, or to another website that recognizes that cookie. Cookies allow a website to recognize your device. Cookies are used for many reasons, such as letting you navigate between pages efficiently, remembering your preferences, and generally to improve your user experience. Cookies are also used to ensure that advertisements you see online are more relevant to you and your interests.

You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. 

## **Ad Networks and “Re-Marketing”**

Wego utililses third party vendors, including Google and Double Click, to collect non-personal information in the form of user and usage metrics when you use a Wego Site. In particular, Wego uses the Google Analytics Display Network Impression Reporting feature.

These tools and technologies collect and analyze certain types of information, including cookies, IP addresses, device and software identifiers, referring and exit URLs, onsite behavior and usage information.   
The third party analytics companies who collect information on the Wego Site(s) may combine the information collected with other information they have independently collected from other websites and/or other online or mobile products and services relating to your activities across their network of websites as well as online and/or mobile products and services. Many of these companies collect and use information under their own privacy policies.

Wego works with third party companies to help us tailor advertising that we think may be of interest to you based on your use of a Wego Site and to otherwise collect and use data about your use of a Wego Site. These companies may deliver ads that might also place cookies and otherwise track user behavior. These companies may use information about user behavior in order to provide customized advertisements across various services and products. In the course of providing these services, products or placing advertisements, these third party companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your computer, and may record information to these cookies based upon your activities on a Wego Site and on third party websites. Each of these companies use this cookie information according to their own privacy and security policies. If you do not wish to have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out as indicated in below. Please note this does not opt you out of being delivered advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.

Using the Ads Settings, you can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Network ads. In addition, you can also prevent your data from being collected or used by Google Analytics using Google Analytics’ [currently available opt outs for the web](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).  
You can also opt out of DoubleClick’s use of cookies by visiting the [DoubleClick opt-out page](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx) or the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

## **Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages. You agree that such posting will constitute sufficient and adequate notice to you of the changes. You agree that your continued use of our products or services after such amendment will constitute your acceptance of and agreement to be bound by the modified policy.

## **Questions or Suggestions**

If you have questions or suggestions email us at [privacy@wego.com](mailto:privacy@wego.com)
